Xavier Marquez

548 S Donovan St Seattle, WA 98108 206 465 9332 xavier.ray.marquez@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A hardworking quick learner with expertise in sales and customer/technical support. My strengths include attention to detail, timeliness, and communication skills. Demonstrates skills in customer support and problem-solving. Works effectively alone or in a team setting. previously employed with the Seattle Mariners in corporate sales/Gameday Handler for Mariners Moose. As well as Employed at Emerald City Pet Rescue as IT Specialist and Retail Associate.

EDUCATION

West Seattle High School

High School Diploma - 2013 to 2017

Accomplishments

- Received a West Seattle Academic Achievement Award.
- Member of the prestigious and highly competitive Foster School of Business Young Executives of Color program. A leadership and mentorship program in which students of color from all over Washington meet and learn from various High-Level Executives of major business and Fortune 500 companies with an emphasis on creating the next generation of business leaders.
- Member of Link Crew at West Seattle High. A competitive leadership program in which Seniors mentor incoming Freshman throughout the year.
- Recommended for Academic Student Body by several teachers for the 2015-2016 school year.

EXPERIENCE

Mascot Handler/Corporate sales, Seattle Mariners

Seattle, WA - 2018-2019

Assisted Mascot Performer with appearance and promotions during game day and Performed as Mariners Moose for outside appearances.

Responsibilities were costume and prop creation/maintenance and game day appearance management and promotion of Mariners moose apparel

Harry the Husky, University of Washington

Seattle, WA - 2017-2018

Represent the University of Washington at select sporting and other events as Harry the Husky.

Retail Associate, Emerald City Pet Rescue

Seattle, WA - 2016-2017

Assisted in Rotation and Restock of store goods,

Responsibilities were Cashier and customer service.

Distribution Center, and IT Specialist, Emerald City Pet Rescue

Seattle, WA - 2017 - 2021

Assist with the logistics and distribution of animal supplies and medication.

Perform general quickbooks server maintenance and basic IT functions throughout the company.

Instructor/Coach, West Seattle Gymnastics Academy

Seattle, WA - 2014 - 2016

Assisted with spotting, teaching, and advising other students under the supervision of an experienced coach. This was a part time position in which I worked with children ages seven to twelve.

Accomplishments

 During my tenure as a volunteer I helped each student improve their overall tumbling skills.

Assistant VolleyBall Coach, Holy Rosary Parish School

Seattle, WA - 2013 to 2015

A seasonal volunteer position in which I assisted with the coaching and refereeing of the 4th through 5th Girls Volleyball Teams. I would call games on weekends and assist the coach during weekday practices.

Accomplishments

- As part of my work with the girls, I saw them accomplish major personal goals and learn to play as a team.
- Our major emphasis was not only teamwork but also an increase of self-esteem and physical ability.

SKILLS

- Bilingual in Spanish and English
- Good Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- Excellent Leadership Skills
- Experience In working with younger children in a gym setting
- Advanced Athletic Skills

CERTIFICATIONS

TIPS Certified exp: 8/20/2022

REFERENCES

Available upon request.